TAP version 13
# Subtest: non-boom and legacy reports have no invented motion check
ok 1 - non-boom and legacy reports have no invented motion check
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.9758
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: notice exposes authored versus achieved movement and source window
ok 2 - notice exposes authored versus achieved movement and source window
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.3251
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: explicit keys are identified as scoped overrides, not silently relabelled
ok 3 - explicit keys are identified as scoped overrides, not silently relabelled
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.1217
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: missing evidence has no invented numeric measurements
ok 4 - missing evidence has no invented numeric measurements
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.1915
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: formatting leaves the compiled evidence unchanged
ok 5 - formatting leaves the compiled evidence unchanged
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.4287
  type: 'test'
  ...
1..5
# tests 5
# suites 0
# pass 5
# fail 0
# cancelled 0
# skipped 0
# todo 0
# duration_ms 82.3407
